Hello.
In this next lecture, we're going to make it to our Planck actor also has their own project artwork
to get started.
Head over to the Warrior animation folder and just create a new folder and call this apple.
Then head inside here and then briefly close on your engine and attached.
In this course, I'm going to make sure to include this image of an apple.
Just select it and drag it into this folder.
Once you've done that, just right.
Click on this image and apply paper to the settings.
Then right click and go spray actions and create a sprite.
Next, if we head back to our player character folder, let's create our Apple projectile.
If I just right click and Go Blueprint class, select an actor and call this apple projectile underscore
beep.
And if we open it up under components, go ahead and look for a paper sprite.
With this selected water source, select the apple that we just imported and scroll down and make it
a collision preset.
No collision.
My apple is a bit small, so if we just scroll up and scale it up to three.
Now, I don't have any cool flipbook animations for my apple.
So to add a cool effect, let's go add a look for rotating movement.
If I just select this and then go simulate, you'll see that my apple is rotating.
So we only use this component to make my apple rotate.
If we go to Z, just put a value of zero here.
So my apple will no longer rotate in the z axis and in Y per value of -180.
And then go simulate.
And that will make it look like the apple is rotating forwards.
You can play around with these values if you want to get a different value.
If I made this something like -600, then it's going to rotate a lot faster.
But I'm happy with -180.
Okay, Next, let's go ahead and look for a fake liver.
Make this decision around our apple.
So decrease its size a bit.
And then finally, we need to add some projectile movement to our apple.
So let's go ahead and look for projectile movement.
And under initial and max speed, I'm going to have a value of 1000.
And in the details, I'm going to make sure it's not affected by gravity.
So I'm look for.
Projectile gravity scale and put this to zero.
Next if we select our sphere cousin.
And scroll down and go on component again over that.
We're going to make it so that if this actor overlaps another actor which has a particular tag, we're
going to apply damage to them.
So other actor but for has tag this one actor has tag and under tag type in enemy.
If this condition is true.
And we're going to apply damage to the other actor.
There's a struggle here and look for apply damage.
The amount of damage we're going to do is going to be one.
And then we're going to destroy this actor.
So drag ahead and look for destroy actor.
Then go compile and we want to go to our skeleton blueprint and our mushroom blueprint.
So let me just find this.
And we're going to give them the tag of enemy to give an extra attack.
Select it here and then under details, look for tag and then we can go advanced, add a new tag and
just click this add element and type in the tag.
So type in enemy and we'll do the same thing for my mushroom blueprint.
So I go here.
So the mushroom itself under details, look for tag, add a new tag and I'll cool this enemy.
We can now compile and save this.